PROFILES

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/kp7742 **GitHub:** github.com/kp7742 **Twitter:** twitter.com/kexecv

EDUCATION

JUN 2013 - MAR 2014

10th Board

R.S.M. Poonawala Sarvajanik Experimental School, Surat, Gujarat, India

JUN 2015 - MAR 2016

12th Board

R.S.M. Poonawala Sarvajanik Experimental School, Surat, Gujarat, India

AUG 2016 - AUG 2020

B.E in Computer Engineering

R.N.G. Patel Institute of Technology, Bardoli, Gujarat, India

SKILLS

C/C++
JAVA
Python
Kotlin
PHP
Frontend – HTML / CSS / JS
Golang

CERTIFICATION

"Google Cloud Platform: Core Infrastructure" Coursera | Mar 2019

"Software Engineering – IT Services"
Aspiring Minds | Sep 2019

KULDIP PATEL

(408) 207-7835 | contact@kuldippatel.dev | San Jose, CA-95113

About Me

I'm 23 years old, Currently studying for MS in Data Analytics in San Jose State University. I have Enthusiasm in Technology, Programming and Cyber Security. I'm also Intermediate Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the Android apps and Web Development and Skilled in C++, Java, PHP, Python and Golang Programming Languages.

EXPERIENCE

SEP 2019

Lead Web/App Developer | Visvesmruti 2019

RNGPIT - Gujarat - India

MAY 2019 - DEC 2019

Internship | D-Link India

D-Link India Limited - Mumbai - India

MAR 2019 - OCT 2019

Student Partner | Internshala

RNGPIT - Gujarat - India

IAN 2019 - AUG 2020

Developer Student Club Community Lead | DSC RNGPIT

RNGPIT - Gujarat - India

PROJECTS

"AIKYAM" | Etherium BlockChain | Feb 2020 Blockchain Based Unique Person Identification System at DotSlash 3.0 Hackathon

"TOBA" | Web Portal + Android App | Mar 2019

Token Based Authentication System for Industry 4.0 Conference

"<u>VSManage</u>" | Website + Android App | Sep 2019 Management System for Technical Festival at Visvesmruti 2019

"WAAutoResponder" | Android App | May 2019
Whatsapp Chat Auto Reply Bot for Automation as Side Project.

"SathChalein" | Android App | Feb 2019
Android App to Bridge gap Between Two Parties for Sharing Trips at DotSlash 2.0

"<u>Visvesmruti App</u>" | Android App | Sep 2018
Official Application for Technical Festival At Visvesmruti 2018, RNGPIT College

"KnowYourCampus" | Android App | Feb 2018
Android App for College Work, TimeTable, Assignment at DotSlash 1.0 Hackathon